http://www.ellatha.com/privacy.asp

Your browser does not support the IFRAME tag.
Yesterday48,83636,924
Top Day267,323(11/03/13)255,979(11/03/13)
Total327,036,467265,299,361
Privacy Statement
Ellatha.com takes your privacy seriously.
NOTICE:
Click here for important information about safe surfing from the Federal Trade Commission.
What this Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy covers Ellatha.com's treatment of personally
identifiable information that Ellatha.com collects when you are on the
Ellatha.com site, and when you use Ellatha.com's services.
This policy also covers Ellatha.com's treatment of any personally
identifiable information that Ellatha.com 's business partners share with
Ellatha.com.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Ellatha.com
does not own or control, or to people that Ellatha.com does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
Ellatha.com collects personally identifiable information when you
register for a Ellatha.com account, when you use certain Ellatha.com
products or services, when you visit Ellatha.com webpages, and when you
enter promotions or sweepstakes. Ellatha.com may also receive personally
identifiable information from our business partners.
When you register with Ellatha.com, we ask for your name, street
address, city/state, zip code, phone number, and email address. Once you register
with Ellatha.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Note: As of 2/14/2017 Signing up has been discontinued, all personal user data has been deleted.
Ellatha.com also automatically receives and records information on our
server logs from your browser including your IP address, Ellatha.com
cookie information and the page you requested.
Ellatha.com uses information for three general purposes: to customize
the advertising and content you see, to fulfill your requests for certain products and
services, and to contact you about specials and new services.
Notice as to the nature and scope of the collection and use of information gathered
by Ellatha.com and business partners, including third party ad networks on any of Ellatha.com's sites;
and Choice to an Internet user of any of Ellatha.com's sites to opt-out from such information collection and use,
including a clear link to the NAI's opt-out page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Ellatha.com will not sell or rent your personally identifiable
information to anyone.
Ellatha.com may send personally identifiable information about you to
other companies or people when:
We need to share your information to provide the product or service you have requested;
We need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Ellatha.com
to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you differently, these
companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we
provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
We respond to subpoenas, court orders or legal process; or
We find that your actions on our web sites violate the Ellatha.com
Terms of Service , or any of our
usage guidelines for specific products or services.
Cookies
Ellatha.com may set and access Ellatha.com cookies on your computer.
Ellatha.com allows other companies that are presenting advertisements
on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies'
use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one.
Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Ellatha.com's cookies.
Ellatha.com uses web beacons to access our cookies within our network
of web sites and in connection with Ellatha.com products and services.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
Ellatha.com gives you the ability to edit your Ellatha.com
Account Information and preferences at any time.
You may request deletion of your Ellatha.com account by sending an
email to Ellatha@Hotmail.com.
Security
Your Ellatha.com Account Information is password-protected for your
privacy and security.
In certain areas Ellatha.com uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to
protect data transmissions.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Ellatha.com may amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial
changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting a
prominent announcement on our pages.
Questions or Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please email your suggestion to: Ellatha@Hotmail.com.
Other Legal Notices: Terms of Service (TOS) - Copyright Notice
Advertisement
Your browser does not support the IFRAME tag.
Online
You will not see this text if your browser supports IFRAME. If you CAN see this, you are in a bad way.
